<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="launch_title">@string/drawer_launch</string>
	<string name="launch_description">
		On this page you can define how you want to launch and hide this application. Perhaps
		you don\'t want others to know that you have installed this application.
	</string>
	<string name="launch_dialer">Dialer Launch</string>
	<string name="launch_dialer_description">
		The dialer of your device could be used to launch this application. All you have to do is call the code
		that you specified below as the launch code for this application. The pin dialog will pop up, from
		where you can enter your vault.
		\n\nNote that if you make mistakes with the launch code, they will appear in your call log. If you call the
		code correctly however, it will be caught and it will not be shown in your call log.
	</string>
	<string name="launch_dialer_use">Use dialer launch</string>
	<string name="launch_dialer_code">Dialer launch code:</string>
	<string name="launch_dialer_hint">Launch code</string>
	<string name="launch_widget">Widget Launch</string>
	<string name="launch_widget_description">
		You could create a widget on your home screen which is invisible. No one will know it is there, except you.
		In order to launch this application, all you have to do is tap the invisible widget 4 times.
		The pin dialog will then pop up, from where you can enter your vault.
	</string>
	<string name="launch_widget_use">Use widget for launch</string>
	<string name="launch_widget_visible_description">
		If you can\'t find the widget anymore, you could add another one as this would make them all temporarily
		visible until you tap on one. Or, you can show them by enabling the checkbox below. Tap the widget on your
		home screen in order to hide it again.
	</string>
	<string name="launch_widget_visible">Make widgets temporarily visible</string>
	<string name="launch_icon">Icon Visibility</string>
	<string name="launch_icon_description">
		If you don\'t want other users to know about the existence of this application on your phone, we could try to
		hide the application icon from the app drawer of your device. However, it will still be visible in the
		\'installed application\' list of your Android Settings. A solution could be to hide this application in plain
		sight. Go to the morphing tab for more information.
		\n\nNOTE: This method will only be enabled if at least one of the below launch methods is enabled.
	</string>
	<string name="launch_icon_disable">Hide application icon</string>
	<string name="launch_disclaimer">WARNING</string>
	<string name="launch_disclaimer_description">
		Note that the above methods don\'t work perfectly for people who know what they are searching for:
		(1) the widget could be found by tapping everywhere a lot, (2) mistakes with dialing the launch code show in the call log
		and therefore could potentially leak your launch code if you are not careful, and finally, (3) the application
		is always shown in the \'installed application\' list of your Android Settings. There is however another way
		to hide this application: check out the morphing tab!
		\n\nNote that if you don\'t remember your launch method, it will be impossible to open up this application. However,
		when using the widget you could also place another one.
	</string>
</resources>